Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Weekly
1895 -- 1968
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UP056
4.8 Linear Feet
62 Volumes
19.78 Gigabytes
2079 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issue of The Tufts Weekly. It covered college and university news, sports, and events. In its earliest days it also had a literary aspect, but was always primarily concerned with news of the campus written by students. The Weekly contained editorials, announcements, advertising, and calendar items of events. With some exceptions, each volume covers one academic year.
The Tufts Weekly was the student newspaper from 1895 through 1968. It was replaced by the Observer in 1969. Four issues of the Tufts News was published in 1912 by the Class of 1913 as a temporary substitute for The Tufts Weekly, cataloged at end of series 1.
Related Materials
UP055, Tufts Observer, DCA
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the purview of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Weekly. It was the student newspaper from 1895 through 1968. It was replaced by the Observer in 1969.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Physical condition. Open for research.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1895; UP056.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Physical condition.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1895; UP056.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 22, 1895; UP056.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    Alpha Kappa Kappa.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 29, 1895; UP056.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1895; UP056.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1895; UP056.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1895; UP056.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 26, 1895; UP056.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1895; UP056.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 10, 1895; UP056.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1895; UP056.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 7, 1896; UP056.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1896; UP056.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 21, 1896; UP056.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 28, 1896; UP056.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 4, 1896; UP056.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1896; UP056.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1896; UP056.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1896; UP056.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1896; UP056.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1896; UP056.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1896; UP056.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1896; UP056.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 14, 1896; UP056.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 22, 1896; UP056.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1896; UP056.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1896; UP056.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1896; UP056.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1896; UP056.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1896; UP056.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1896; UP056.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 9, 1896; UP056.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 16, 1896; UP056.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1896; UP056.001.001.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.78 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1896; UP056.001.001.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.59 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1896; UP056.001.001.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.54 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1896; UP056.001.001.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.64 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1896; UP056.001.001.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.47 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1896; UP056.001.001.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.47 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1896; UP056.001.001.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.42 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1896; UP056.001.001.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.75 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 24, 1896; UP056.001.001.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.64 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1896; UP056.001.001.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.70 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1896; UP056.001.001.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.17 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1896; UP056.001.001.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.19 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 22, 1896; UP056.001.001.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.11 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1897; UP056.001.001.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.36 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1897; UP056.001.001.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.81 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 26, 1897; UP056.001.001.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.27 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 2, 1897; UP056.001.001.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.96 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1897; UP056.001.001.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.71 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1897; UP056.001.001.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.28 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1897; UP056.001.001.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.16 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1897; UP056.001.001.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.43 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1897; UP056.001.001.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.35 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1897; UP056.001.001.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.11 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1897; UP056.001.001.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.08 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1897; UP056.001.001.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.58 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 14, 1897; UP056.001.001.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.00 Megabytes (Box 1)
    [Alumni 1897]
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1897; UP056.001.001.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.06 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1897; UP056.001.001.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.35 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1897; UP056.001.001.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.37 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1897; UP056.001.001.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.26 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1897; UP056.001.001.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.36 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1897; UP056.001.001.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.49 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1897; UP056.001.001.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.56 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 9, 1897; UP056.001.001.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.16 Megabytes (Box 1)
    Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1897; UP056.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1897; UP056.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1897; UP056.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1897; UP056.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1897; UP056.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1897; UP056.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1897; UP056.001.001.00074 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1897; UP056.001.001.00075 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1897; UP056.001.001.00076 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 22, 1897; UP056.001.001.00077 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1898; UP056.001.001.00078 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1898; UP056.001.001.00079 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 26, 1898; UP056.001.001.00080 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 2, 1898; UP056.001.001.00081 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 9, 1898; UP056.001.001.00082 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1898; UP056.001.001.00083 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1898; UP056.001.001.00084 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1898; UP056.001.001.00085 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1898; UP056.001.001.00086 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1898; UP056.001.001.00087 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1898; UP056.001.001.00088 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 30, 1898; UP056.001.001.00089 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 13, 1898; UP056.001.001.00090 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 20, 1898; UP056.001.001.00091 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 27, 1898; UP056.001.001.00092 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 4, 1898; UP056.001.001.00093 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 11, 1898; UP056.001.001.00094 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 18, 1898; UP056.001.001.00095 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 25, 1898; UP056.001.001.00096 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 1, 1898; UP056.001.001.00097 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 8, 1898; UP056.001.001.00098 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1898; UP056.001.002.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.19 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Open for research.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 12, 1898; UP056.001.002.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.24 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1898; UP056.001.002.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1898; UP056.001.002.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.83 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1898; UP056.001.002.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.58 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1898; UP056.001.002.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1898; UP056.001.002.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 23, 1898; UP056.001.002.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.87 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1898; UP056.001.002.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1898; UP056.001.002.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 21, 1898; UP056.001.002.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.29 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1899; UP056.001.002.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 18, 1899; UP056.001.002.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.68 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 25, 1899; UP056.001.002.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 1, 1899; UP056.001.002.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.49 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 8, 1899; UP056.001.002.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.72 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Daniel Gustavius Abbott (1886). Death of, January 30, 1899. (page 2) [Alpha Tau Omega] Purchased Joy House, corner of Curtis Avenue and Curtis St.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1899; UP056.001.002.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alpha Tau Omega] Report that ATO bought Joy House false.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 22, 1899; UP056.001.002.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1899; UP056.001.002.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.41 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1899; UP056.001.002.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.24 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1899; UP056.001.002.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1899; UP056.001.002.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1899; UP056.001.002.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1899; UP056.001.002.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 19, 1899; UP056.001.002.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.79 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1899; UP056.001.002.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.06 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1899; UP056.001.002.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1899; UP056.001.002.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.99 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1899; UP056.001.002.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1899; UP056.001.002.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.21 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1899; UP056.001.002.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 7, 1899; UP056.001.002.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.93 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 14, 1899; UP056.001.002.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.92 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1899; UP056.001.002.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.19 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1899; UP056.001.002.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1899; UP056.001.002.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1899; UP056.001.002.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.25 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1899; UP056.001.002.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1899; UP056.001.002.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.47 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1899; UP056.001.002.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.23 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1899; UP056.001.002.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1899; UP056.001.002.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1899; UP056.001.002.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.14 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1900; UP056.001.002.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.53 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 17, 1900; UP056.001.002.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alpha Kappa Kappa] Fraternity buys house on West Newton Street.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 24, 1900; UP056.001.002.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.40 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 31, 1900; UP056.001.002.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.56 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 7, 1900; UP056.001.002.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.46 Megabytes (Box 2)
    [Alumni] System of registration arranged by faculty committee
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1900; UP056.001.002.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1900; UP056.001.002.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.87 Megabytes (Box 2)
    Alpha Kappa Delta. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1900; UP056.001.002.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.73 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1900; UP056.001.002.00052; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.10 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1900; UP056.001.002.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.22 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 28, 1900; UP056.001.002.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.77 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1900; UP056.001.002.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.60 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1900; UP056.001.002.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.35 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1900; UP056.001.002.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.50 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1900; UP056.001.002.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.74 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1900; UP056.001.002.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.04 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 23, 1900; UP056.001.002.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.07 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 6, 1900; UP056.001.002.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 20, 1900; UP056.001.002.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.96 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 3, 1900; UP056.001.002.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.28 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 10, 1900; UP056.001.002.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.22 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1900; UP056.001.002.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.02 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 24, 1900; UP056.001.002.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.91 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1900; UP056.001.002.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.05 Megabytes (Box 2)
    All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1900; UP056.001.002.00068; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.82 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1900; UP056.001.002.00069; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.63 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1900; UP056.001.002.00070; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.64 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1900; UP056.001.002.00071; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.78 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1900; UP056.001.002.00072; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.75 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1901; UP056.001.002.00073; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.70 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1901; UP056.001.002.00074; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.52 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 23, 1901; UP056.001.002.00075; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.62 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 30, 1901; UP056.001.002.00076; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.33 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 6, 1901; UP056.001.002.00077; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.62 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1901; UP056.001.002.00078; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.79 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1901; UP056.001.002.00079; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.97 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1901; UP056.001.002.00080; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.81 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1901; UP056.001.002.00081; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.95 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1901; UP056.001.002.00082; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.03 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1901; UP056.001.002.00083; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.36 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 10, 1901; UP056.001.002.00084; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.50 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1901; UP056.001.002.00085; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.17 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1901; UP056.001.002.00086; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.90 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1901; UP056.001.002.00087; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.30 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1901; UP056.001.002.00088; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.77 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1901; UP056.001.002.00089; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 22, 1901; UP056.001.002.00090; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 29, 1901; UP056.001.002.00091; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.92 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 5, 1901; UP056.001.002.00092; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.94 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 12, 1901; UP056.001.002.00093; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.55 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 19, 1901; UP056.001.002.00094; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.89 Megabytes (Box 2)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 26, 1901; UP056.001.003.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
    All Around Club. [Allen House] Rooming accomodations for women students.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 3, 1901; UP056.001.003.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.21 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 10, 1901; UP056.001.003.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.69 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1901; UP056.001.003.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.20 Megabytes (Box 3)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 24, 1901; UP056.001.003.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.92 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1901; UP056.001.003.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1901; UP056.001.003.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.65 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1901; UP056.001.003.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.76 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1901; UP056.001.003.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.55 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1901; UP056.001.003.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.25 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1901; UP056.001.003.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.77 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1901; UP056.001.003.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 3)
    [Admissions, 1901] New Entrance Requirements.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1902; UP056.001.003.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.07 Megabytes (Box 3)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega; Alumni dance, pg 1
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1902; UP056.001.003.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.81 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 23, 1902; UP056.001.003.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.63 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 30, 1902; UP056.001.003.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.71 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 6, 1902; UP056.001.003.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.92 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1902; UP056.001.003.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.94 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 20, 1902; UP056.001.003.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.45 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1902; UP056.001.003.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.39 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1902; UP056.001.003.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.76 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1902; UP056.001.003.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.23 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1902; UP056.001.003.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.54 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1902; UP056.001.003.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.73 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 3, 1902; UP056.001.003.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1902; UP056.001.003.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.35 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1902; UP056.001.003.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.72 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1902; UP056.001.003.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.09 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1902; UP056.001.003.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.23 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1902; UP056.001.003.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.03 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 22, 1902; UP056.001.003.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.26 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 29, 1902; UP056.001.003.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.34 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 4, 1902; UP056.001.003.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.29 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 11, 1902; UP056.001.003.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.12 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 19, 1902; UP056.001.003.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.88 Megabytes (Box 3)
    Commencement Supplement
  - Tufts Weekly, September 24, 1902; UP056.001.003.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.33 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1902; UP056.001.003.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.66 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1902; UP056.001.003.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.67 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 16, 1902; UP056.001.003.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.74 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1902; UP056.001.003.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.80 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1902; UP056.001.003.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.08 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1902; UP056.001.003.00042; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.13 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 13, 1902; UP056.001.003.00043; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.01 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 20, 1902; UP056.001.003.00044; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.00 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1902; UP056.001.003.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.05 Megabytes (Box 3)